What the hell are you blabbering?
Go!
Who are you guys?
They're pouring petrol.
- Put it inside.
No, please no...
He's coming to run over us.
You're hitting us!
Hello...
Name is Veera...
Nickname is braveheart...
Bravest of the brave...
He's Rama... he's Ravana...
He's a man with characters...
Both are in him and
he's different at different times...
lf you were born like me...
Had you lived my life...
lf you'd waged my battle...
You're a Rama...
you're Ravana... you're both...
Sir, DSP wants to talk to you.
Tell me Hemant.
l don't know how to tell you...
an accident happened here sir...
What's it, tell me Hemant?
Boat accident sir...
ln that...
When? Where?
- Just a while ago.
Near Pakumetla jetty.
Your wife Ragini has been kidnapped.
We've eye witness sir.
Who?
- Veera's men.
They've taken her in boat
towards Nallamala hills.
l've sent a search team.
lnformed lG.
He assured to send state alert.
ls anyone here?
All are men here,
will not show mercy on a woman too.
Who is it? Who is it?
Fresh chicken gravy,
want to taste it?
What do you've to do with me?
Who is it?
l'm not scared of you.
Unable to fight like a man,
you kidnapped a woman
like me stealthily.
Victory awaits you,
don't get dejected heart...
There's liberation to this life
and an eternal place...
Life is useful...
With devotion only...
There's strength of
my tribe in heart...
No vengeance...
Victory awaits you,
don't get dejected heart...
There's liberation to this life
and an eternal place...
This is your life's biggest mistake.
- Life is useful...
Kidnapping me.
She may get drowned.
Nothing will happen, still 14 hours
are there to blow the conch.
Let her take three dips.
Can't you see it's a police jeep?
Why are you waving hands?
What happened to your voice?
Get up and open the gate.
Today l really...
- You bull!
Why are you singing without
bothering who is here?
Missed the rhythm, boy.
Police have come with
a long fleet of jeeps...
Bloody drunkard!
Go now and come back tomorrow...
What's that?
Shut your gob and open the gate.
- As you wish.
lntelligent don't become great men...
Brainless police don't have a gun...
Catch him.
- Try if you can.
l really admire and
love to serve you...
lf you don't come down,
l'll come up and shoot you.
Let me see it!
Escape!
There!
There! Look!
He's jumping there!
Since 28 years sir.
DFO has good words for you.
- Yes sir.
lt seems you've a record
in the department. - yes sir.
ln getting highest number
of suspensions. - Now also sir.
Just two months,
it'll be over just like that sir.
You know this forest very well
or just to booze only.
ls all this monkeying because of liquor
or taking orders from someone.
You're government servant,
moreover SP,
28 encounters, number one
encounter specialist, right sir?
l'm also a government servant,
l'm waiting here for 3 hours
for you sir.
l'll not let you enter forest alone.
He's not trustworthy sir, a drunkard,
l suspect he's Veera's man.
l don't think he knows
anything about the forest.
l don't trust this man,
he's short tempered.
Half baked man, he doesn't know
anything about forest or anything.
1l'll slap you.
Slap me? From Guntur district?
l love it. But l don't like you.
l'll get rid of you in the forest.
l'll cut you to pieces
if you blabber again.
Who do you think l'm?
Veera... Veeraiah...
born in Penugonda.
FlR's have been registered in all
police stations around the place.
Totally 63 cases.
l was specially transferred here
to put a check to him.
Neither l'm here with a welcome
party nor as your escort.
l know you don't like all that.
l heard many don't like
police in this region,
is it true?
l'm going to stay away
from such people.
Far away!
Except one man!
He has another name here... Ravana.
Ten headed Ravana.
lf the eldest is struck,
entire structure will fall.
Shall we aim the eldest?
Elder brother Singaraju,
another face of Veera,
he presides over the village courts,
younger brother Chakri,
studied upto lntermediate,
to help elder brothers,
people responsible for any brutal
assault ten minutes prior,
or within 5 minutes after it,
Veera will be there to seek revenge.
You know so much,
why have you left him till now?
We were waiting for
such a daring SP.
lf top brass is shivering in fear,
what can we do?
He's protector God to half and
the other half can't fight him.
According to law,
Veera is a criminal.
Extremist... terrorist.
That's it.
You've been given this uniform
to protect us from such men.
Why do you keep quiet?
Why don't you shoot him down?
l got an opportunity
to catch this Ravana.
l missed it.
But this time l'll not spare him.
l'll not come back without
putting an end to Veera's life.
Till then, be brave Ragini.
Sir... sir... please stop the vehicle.
SP sir, just a minute.
You don't just see with eyes
in forest, see with your ears too.
Don't search in water,
come here.
Who tied you up?
Gagged too.
Speak... were you the boatman?
Unable to breath? Can't speak?
Get me some water.
You will come...
- What?
You will come and...
- We'll come and...
... will untie me.
- He said we'll come to untie him.
Come on tell me...
if you've sense...
. . without wasting time...
- Without wasting time...
Come to the Nallamala hills in the east.
- Come to Nallamala hills in the east.
He tied him, gagged his mouth
and told him the place also.
Are we searching him
or is he taking us to him?
Are you telling the truth?
To Nallamala hill top.
- He wants at Nallamala hill top.
Tell everything to sir.
Did you see her?
How is she?
ls she hurt?
Was she crying?
l'll not come... leave me.
Come.
- Leave me.
Leave me.
What are you doing?
l'll not come.
Leave me.
Taking a child's life,
are you shouting here?
l'll break you into pieces.
Bloody woman!
We must get ruined but
you must live happily.
Our people's curse will not spare you.
Look, you'll get ruined,
you'll never come good in life.
l'm cursing you, you must get
crucified for your husband's sins.
Who are you to kill me?
Who gave you that right?
Why do you pull women
into your men's fight?
My life is mine.
lt's mine.
- Will you stop it?
l hate sounds.
l hear ten voices in my head.
Veera, don't think,
gun her down immediately.
l'll not die.
My foot! Can't escape fate.
Let you, your husband and
the world know.
You can't kill me.
There's commotion in head,
forest cries,
ferocious dance,
a question on one side and
an answer on the other side,
philosophy, anger, accusation,
laugh, patience, myriad of emotions.
You can't kill me.
lf you die with smile, next 7 births
you'll take birth with a smile.
l'll not die.
lf you get cold, for 7 births...
- My death is not in your hands.
You silly woman!
When did you come into this world...
You made me lose my sense...
Though this Nallamala forest
is very big...
Though a match stick is very small...
lf this match stick lights up...
Won't this Nallamala forest
be reduced to ashes?
l lost my life seeing
those shivering lips...
l'm going away forelorn...
return back my heart O maiden...
Though you're beyond my reach,
come into my arms...
Enough, my ears are bursting.
Stop it.
l'm not crying.
Will you stop crying or not?
Come with me.
Find another woman for it,
aren't you ashamed of it?
Like a coward,
you abducted a woman.
l think all the bad words
were coined for you only.
Excellent Veera!
You've stopped crying, right?
Can tolerate a woman
using bad words,
but can't bear a woman's cries, right?
Sun and moon are at one place...
lt's true, today darkness too
has shadows...
Though l know you're a ball of fire,
l want to feel the heat...
This is not new to the old world...
Can't stop the faceless restriction...
This is a line of law
we created ourselves...
Find number of bones it has...
Even sheep won't dare jump,
why did you take the plunge?
Why did you save me then?
Body wouldn't have become
feed to crows too.
Why did you then try to shoot me?
You were fated to die in my hands.
But some fool altered it.
Pray, if you trust in God.
You'll die because of me.
That's the destiny of fate.
Nobody... what did you say?
Nobody can wipe me out.
When sun emerges from clouds,
lotus will bloom...
The love that has sprouted in you
doesn't care for anything...
Poor Veera, you can't
find the difference...
Though it is sin,
there's no going back...
With fires of death engulfing me...
lt's you in my heart and soul...
Though l'm buried,
you'll still be in my heart...
Here's come our leader!
Greetings sir.
Bless me.
- Bless you son.
Now l know why didn't shoot her.
l was foolish not to realise it.
With one bullet it would be over,
either me or he would've
gone to jail for few years.
the problem would've been over.
You too would've left her
thinking about future.
Why do you think l left her?
For 14 hours torture, SP has come
with 5 truck loads of police men.
lf we keep him o toes for 14 days,
your idea is great.
l was standing with
a pistol pointed at her,
a minute or two she would've died,
she was standing fearless
like a dead body.
Not a faint of fear, brother.
How can l kill a fearless woman?
Brother, would you've pulled the
trigger if you were in my place?
l can't think so much.
You want me to cut a goat
and prepare a soup.
lt'll rock you.
lf any boys here misbehave,
l can thrash or send them to jail,
tell me, l'll do it in minutes.
Women, fear are beyond me, brother.
She's the new sister.
What are you looking at?
Clear out.
You won't get clothes here,
l found a leaf of my size,
put stitches to it and
drape yourself in it.
Uncle...
- Clear out kids!
You won't laugh for a joke,
don't fear at a pointed gun,
what sort of a life is it?
Food! Will you atleast respect this?
Throw into the dustbin.
Am l a dog?
To tie and feed me.
We are struggling for
generations for a meal only.
So proud? Arrogance of rich.
ls what you're doing good?
Women remain women.
Feeling pity at your plight,
are you arguing with me?
Look, my wife too never
shouted at me.
lf you're hungry,
eat it or else leave it.
As you wish.
ls salt okay?
Be loyal to us all your life.
For my size.
That's a pistol.
Yes, it's gun.
Guiding us to their hideout.
Greetings sir.
Our SP is here to talk to you.
You talk to them sir.
Where is he?
Where is Veeraiah?
Veeraiah is a great man.
He never speaks loudly sir.
What's that language?
Enough of it, go away.
He's brave as his name,
he fights like a real warrior.
He hacks anyone.
These men don't know anything,
he's very kind hearted man,
he's lovable than a mother,
he's straightforward and
so gets into trouble easily.
With outsiders too, like with us.
Very clever, he says anything
in shortest terms.
Are you his brother?
- Girls swoon over him, sir.
Not for all girls, go now.
Not praising him too much,
but he's great in donning any role,
very good drama actor.
Folk artiste too.
When starts talking,
he'll make you laugh to tears.
lt's crying.
Very dangerous man, sir.
A goon, a loafer, hacking people,
communal clashes,
creating trouble,
he doesn't everything.
When he starts playing drums...
He's God of Death in flesh.
Death is inevitable, sir.
Enough of it, ten people have told
ten different things and confused us.
l'm feeling giddy.
ls it hand? Very hard.
Tough.
Matched horoscopes
and 7 compatibilities,
but failed to check if hands
and legs are soft.
Your mother-in-law.
My dear, this is a policeman's hand.
Very sharp hands.
ls it fired or non-fired hands?
Touch heart and say.
l'll tell my dear.
Go away.
This is not false...
l'm yours in light...
ln the depth of my eyes...
there's magnet to draw you near...
Falling for you and your heart,
few more thing made... O my friend...
l've grown thin...
have you forgotten me, my partner...
My beauty is glowing and growing...
When my beauty & you unite, it's bliss...
May l become part of you...
Should l've to tell you
my wishes and breath?
Should l say only when you ask?
lf l hear in your heart, it's yes from me.
My lips are splitting with unfulfilled
desires, why don't you rule over it?
lt's character of Telugu to
row out of romantic seas...
Don't you know to convert wild
streams of desires into docile lakes?
l didn't try to escape hearing
Veera's name, l came with you.
Why are you lamenting? Come.
l'm scared... Goddess Kali.
Come out.
Come out... come.
Stand like a man.
l'm innocent.
l swear l'm not responsible for it.
- Tell the truth.
Had a nice journey?
What is this? Watch?
Presented by me?
l gave you my sister too,
where is she now?
Where is she?
l don't know.
- Did you lose her?
Answer him.
Why are you still wearing the watch?
You lost my sister but
keeping the watch safely.
Please don't kill me, l'm innocent.
Where is my sister?
- Trust me.
Singanna, tell him to spare me.
Veeraiah, l'm telling truth,
l'm innocent.
All of give poses like real villains,
the photo must scare them.
Don't act smart,
take a photo quickly.
Will you take a photo or shall l take
your head?- l'll take it.
lf you don't move, l'll take a photo.
One punch, she'll keep quiet.
lt's a scarecrow.
Even crows will not get scared of it.
Don't take a step further.
Where's the nearest hospital?
Get the truck here.
l want first aid box, and pain killers.
Blood is still bleeding, immediate
hospitalization can save him.
Leave for alone for few minutes.
Aren't you Veera's sister's husband?
He cut my hand sir.
- Didn't spare brother-in-law too?
He's not a man but beast.
He's a beast.
- ls it?
What's the message to send
brother-in-law with a hand cut?
l can't bear this pain,
take me to the hospital.
What's he trying to say with
a scarecrow in sari and you behind it?
What is he trying to say?
No... sir... no...
Why did he send you?
lt's paining sir...
Trying to scare me?
Will he cut my hand too?
Where are you?
lf you don't come quickly,
he'll kill me.
Are you testing your wife's courage?
l'm not brave.
l'm just acting brave.
l'm shouting.
Wearing a mask.
You're here, aren't you?
You didn't go away, did you?
Answer me.
When will you come?
Madam, how much ever you may cry,
no God will come to save you.
Your husband will also not come.
Rice and onions, have it.
Eat and sleep,
atleast your anger will ease.
You come, she'll eat.
Tape is on, speak.
- ls it running?- Speak.
SP sir, greetings.
Are you fine, sir?
l expect you're not.
We are not fine because
of officers like you.
l'm Veeraiah, poor man,
illiterate man,
we are not born in high society,
but still l'm your enemy,
villain to you.
Did you see the photo?
Did you recognise her?
l shot the photograph
in day light for you only.
Keep it safely in purse,
you'll may not get again, right?
lf your wife doesn't return,
atleast the photo will be with you.
Why are you getting angry?
ls it paining your now?
ls it hurting your heart severely?
For kidnapping your wife,
you wreck havoc with men and might.
Your women are diamonds and
our women are just stones, right?
SP sir, pray to God,
that your wife shouldn't face
what my sister had faced.
Be careful with the photo.
lsn't anyone there?
Stop! Where are you going?
Be a good girl and
sleep silently on one place.
Did you hear me?
Forest parrot... forest parrot...
What for these cries?
Will it become a drop?
Will it strike like thunder?
Will it vanish?
Will it gain strength to fly away?
Fly out of the garden...
Even lightning could make me shiver...
Who is this parrot?
Where did this parrot come from?
Creating ripples in heart...
My heart is going through
the pangs of separation...
Die!
Rajakka, come up.
Veera is here.
Move it... move it...
lsn't she like our Mangamma
and Guruvamma in this sari?- Yes.
Send me back or tie me up.
lf you walk with us in hot for few days,
you'll become dark like us.
Veera, see how angrily
she's looking at you.
Guruvamma! Why don't you
stay back here only?
Stay with us only.
Why are you leaving silently?
Answer me and go.
Will you stay or not?
Where's your gun?
Take it out... shoot me.
That's better than these questions.
Okay, l mustn't ask like this.
SP shouldn't have met you,
he shouldn't have married you,
he shouldn't have come here,
he shouldn't have done
what he did here,
l shouldn't have kidnapped
you in anger,
l shouldn't have thought
of killing you,
you shouldn't have jumped
down from hill,
l shouldn't have followed you.
When you opened your eyes,
my life shouldn't have come back to me.
Everything has happened,
can't change anything now.
l can't change the path
my heart has taken.
Can't change anything instantly.
Will you stay?
Had you not been married?
Would you've stayed with me?
Forest food?
Maize and tubers?
Arrange for feast.
Make with what's available.
lsnit it Akash?
You can't leave it behind also,
the leftover food may
lead them to us.
But Veeraiah knows
every step we take here.
A forest bird is taking
messages to Veera.
SP is coming, he's coming
towards east with a platoon.
Anyone of you seen the bird?
Did you see Ranjan?
How long it's going on?
How many messages have you sent him?
l didn't get you sir.
Which side we are coming?
How many in the squad?
Sir, l didn't...
Tell me now.
How dare you manhandle
a police lnspector?
Aren't you ashamed to call
yourself a police man?
l'll not care even if you're
my senior officer.
Where is Veera?
- l don't know sir.
Take me to Veeraiah.
ln 6 months or a year,
you'll get transferred,
we've to live here only.
My brothers and sisters
have to study here,
who will protect them?
He's right sir.
- Will you betray the department?
He too is right.
l know the way but don't know
if Veera will be there or not.
Just show us the way,
we'll catch Veera.
Check what happened...
- The tank is open here.
Move... move...
Sugar!
Sugar in diesel tank.
ln all three trucks, how could
they do it while on move?
l don't know sir.
Villagers from neighbouring
hamlet, shepherds.
They use this way to cross the hill.
This is SP's tent.
We've a problem here.
They have sabotaged trucks.
The goat treaded into
the wrong path...
lt got trapped...
What shall l cut?
Tongue or nose?
How about ear?
Catch him... tonsure his head.
- No brother...
l beg you, please leave me.
Tonsure his head.
Chakri lost the challenge
with Singanna.
He challenged we can't come
back alive from police camps.
Tonsure!
l saw your SP's tent.
He keeps... your photo.
Not yours but mine.
lna villain's pose,
like old screen villain Rajanala.
Princess!
A demon's photo in SP's tent.
Take him on a donkey.
Catch him!
lf he gets jealousy...
Kill him...
lf anyone points at you...
Break his fingers...
Till yesterday the law was yours...
From today it's ours...
We were looked down upon,
now we are soaring into skies...
We'll feed a hungry man amply...
We'll behead if anyone asks
for share in property...
Will anyone obey the draconian laws?
When lightning and thunders strike,
the sky will be shattered...
Who will dare to usurp our lands?
Our clan is merciful on
poisonous snakes too...
We know to punish the
violators by naturally...
We are brave children
of Mother Nature...
Taming raging bulls
are my trophies...
The only property given
by old father is bravery...
The air is filled with
scent of fish...
The water here is bridge
of wine to heaven...
We live with nothing but just life...
There's no one break our unity
in any generation...
lf you lose happiness,
you're the poorest of poor...
We'll not change a bit...
The red mud producing crops
is nothing but our blood...
Look at me!
Can you hear me?
Open your eyes.
Great! You can't escape
but helping him!
What are you planning to do with him?
We'll send him to hell on a bull.
Won't you see anyone as humans?
When will you people
stop taking vengeance?
When will you rich people
stop atrocities?
You can see only his
uniform and his job.
He has a heart and good characters.
He loves his mother and fears too.
Why are you torturing him?
Kill him instantly.
Kill him... kill him... shoot him...
Don't think, shoot him.
You want to know the reason, right?
Answer her.
A brave afraid of mother.
A man who respects women.
What did you with Vennela?
Tell her.
Who is Vennela?
The girl who changed your fate.
lsn't she asking you?
Who is Vennela?
My father's progeny.
But not of my mother.
My father's second wife's daughter.
Clever and brave girl.
The only one who isn't afraid of Veera.
She fell in love with a boy.
He too is from a rich family like you.
Veera arranged their marriage
after much pleas and cajoling.
That was the first marriage
in our family.
You know how happy she was?
When lightning struck...
l was perplexed...
Don't know why l got a bad idea...
lt was a red cloth... .
that struck my heart...
Mother, another sister has
come to apply henna.
Tell her to go in.
lf Veera sees, he'll kill us.
You look great in sari and blouse.
You wanted to see the lion,
so here l am.
That's why l've come to your place.
You came in like a coward dancing
like a girl among women.
So you managed to escape.
Had my brothers seen you,
you'll be dead.
l know Judo and Karate,
learnt it in school.
White belt holder,
no man can beat me.
No man can beat you?
What do you say now?
What's this?
Have you gone mad?
You said no man can dare touch you.
Close the door,
someone may see me.
lf your folks see me, l'm dead.
Show your Karate prowess.
Mad girl! Don't open the door.
Why? ls the groom afraid?
She-devil! Listen to me.
Shouldn't the world know
that you're a wrestler?
Bloody!
Why are you using bad words?
Shouldn't l?
- Hide!- Why?
My brother.
- Where?- Hide l say.
Where do you want me to go?
Should your goon brother come now?
Open the door.
- Hide l say.
No, l can't open the door now.
Where's the back door?
- Who is inside?
Who is inside?
- Who else will be there?
l and my shadow.
Someone came to apply henna,
l know it.
l'm changing.
- How can you change with henna?
Brother-in-law!
What are you doing here?
lt's not his fault,
l asked him to come.
He came running here.
l challenged him to dare come here.
So, you've come in skirt and half sari.
What are you doing among women?
Just like that...
- He held my hand.
Who?
Come down.
Come.
With which hand you
held my sister's hand?
Don't harm him.
Singaraju brother promised
to buy a bike as dowry.
lt'll be like circus if he rides
bike with one hand.
Should've thought about it earlier?
Which hand?
Open your eyes.
See the watch.
Still 48 hours for the marriage.
Till then keep your hand
safely with yourself.
lf not you may have to
tie the knot with one hand.
Go now.
Go!
Tell him, if not l think
he'll sleep here only.
Coward!
Garland the goat!
The meat broth is boiling...
Let wine run uninterrupted...
The lady yearns you,
tie the knot with her...
The girl is red like apple and
the groom is like blackberry...
First exchange the garlands
and then change your sari...
She's like Goddess Janaki to look
but Soorpanaka on bed...
The crazy boy has fallen
for her deadly charm...
The young maiden is like tender
lemon but very talkative...
Let the marriage band play...
Let the girl grow up
into woman...
Come girls, brother-in-law is here
to hold umbrellas to brothers-in-law...
The heroine is here as her
sister-in-law holds the sari end...
Let the marriage music play...
Father told me to seek
your blessings.
No cries and melodrama please.
As if you're great NTR,
to make every girl cry on seeing you.
Brother-in-law knows it, right?
Once given goods will
not be taken back.
Brother.
Please come.
People like you're not allowed.
Your kinsman invited us,
we came to bless the couple.
Bless them?
Son-in-law... Son-in-law...
Move... give way.
Play the band... clap your hands...
sing and dance... make merry...
l beg you sir, please don't do it.
We beg you sir, spare them.
Leave them sir.
Brother!
Dev will never shoot without
a valid reason.
l'm sure the mistake will not be his.
lt was all my mistake.
Eight people were pulling me.
But still l shouldn't have
left Vennela alone.
lt should've struck my mind.
l should've known it.
l didn't expect her husband will
escape on seeing the police.
Don't go... don't go...
The man who's afraid of mother
took my sister to police station.
You can't go out from here till you
tell the whereabouts of your brother.
Will you tell on your own?
l'll not show mercy even as a girl.
Open your mouth.
Tell me.
You're a police man, aren't you?
Sniff and find him.
l'll cut it.
He dragged her to the station.
Wasn't it you who took her to station?
You took her, right?
Are you hurt seriously?
Aren't you able to talk?
No problem, you can't fight with me.
l can say anything,
you can't answer me.
Did you see my new husband,
sister-in-law?
He ran away in fear.
He ran away leaving me behind.
Who wants such a husband, brother?
Why did l wish to marry?
l should've remained
unmarried like you.
Who are these police bastards?
Who are they to ruin my life?
l wasn't scared.
Your new husband has ran away,
they asked who would l wish to
spend the first night with, brother?
l used all bad words.
l begged them saying it's sin.
l couldn't take it anymore, brother.
l thought it was just a dream,
l could go home after waking up.
But they didn't leave me.
l shouted... l begged them...
l cried... they didn't leave me.
They avenged all the night.
Everything is ruined.
Everything is gone, brother.
l am ruined, brother.
Slowly... slowly...
Get a rug.
- Getting it sir.
Nothing happened to you.
Nothing... nothing is on.
No hair, no clothes, no honour.
They took everything.
Hemant, you're breathing...
you're talking...
You still have feeling of touch.
Hair will grow again.
You don't worry.
- l asked for a rug.
Are you deaf?
Can you hear me?
lf we take him to camp and
give a peg he'll regain.
Hold him.
Okay sir.
He's in this shape for
few hours of custody.
Madam is with them for 8 days now.
- Stop it l say.
That's what l'm also saying, sir.
Enough sir.
- Take him to base camp.
lf entire battalion goes to forest,
even insects will know.
This will be the result,
he'll take each one of us and kill.
Have you got any other idea?
- l do have sir.
lf you permit me.
Give me courage.
Don't let me my anger subside.
Only that is protecting me.
Don't let them be affectionate
towards me.
l'm praying you.
Show bad in bad light.
Don't show it as good.
Give me strength to fight.
Strength to get angry.
lt's not difficult to you.
Did l disturb your prayers?
What sort of man is he? Your SP.
ls he a good man?
Very good man?
He's God like man.
Satisfied?
One minute.
God means... real God.
lncarnation of God?
ls he flawless man?
Even ten heads can't
stand against him, right?
Nobody can dare go near him.
How does he look like?
Fair and tall?
l'm sure he would be handsome.
Anyway he's God!
How can he be different?
l want to see him.
Once... somehow.
l want to see how God will look like.
l must ask him,
why did he hurry so fast?
ls he affectionate?
Does he laugh and make you laugh?
You... like him.
l'm jealousy.
Unable to digest it.
Did your God feel jealous at anytime?
Only Veeraiah will feel jealous.
l'm beastOtough guy.
A villager...
belong to deprived class.
l thought l'm no compare
to you, and your God.
But the jealous has made me
greater than you all.
O God! This demon,
has it become greater than mother,
father, desire and everything else?
Madam, l'm forest guard...
You'll eat gooseberries, right?
Bite the onion and
gulp the gooseberry.
Take it as a feast.
SP sir, your husband sent
me to locate you.
l searched the entire forest,
SP's wife is safe,
he gave me something,
l kept it in my pocket.
What's that noise?
Madam... here... up!
Look up!
Trust me.
lf you say yes, l'll carry you
to SP sir on my shoulders.
Why didn't he come?
He's just 5 kms away.
Special team is very large,
very noisy team.
Forest people can hear them.
What are you thinking?
They are tough guys, mad fellows.
Just say yes, let's cheat them
and escape from here.
Bloody fool!
Don't harm him.
l'm still here only, right?
l'll cut you like a goat,
will you cheat me?
Veera, l can hear funeral band,
l'm hearing sounds that l shouldn't.
l can hear SP's foot sounds,
he's coming.
l'm warning you to be careful.
l'm SP's man but l support you.
Because you touched my heart.
Did you see them?
Did you see their faces?
They will do anything for you.
They will die for you.
- Will you do it?
They must.
Because you did so much to them.
l'm asking you only one thing,
why are you taking back their lives?
You're the one to die now.
One more bottle and you'll die.
Send back SP's wife,
stop this fight here.
l'll see all the cases are dropped.
lf l don't send her back.
Keep quiet.
Coming back to square one.
Do you want me to say it?
End of you, total destruction,
annihilation.
Everything will be over.
Can't you advice him, elder brother?
He's talking about destruction
and annihilation,
should l get scared?
Are you scared, Rangaiah?
l'm shivering.
Are you scared?
You scared?
No... nobody here is scared.
What do you want me to do?
lf you hit a silent dog with a stone,
it's bound to bite you.
That tall tree, pull a branch down
and leave, it'll rebound.
Are threats new to us?
You've been doing it since long.
They hit us and we fought back.
They raised sticks on us
and we too raised.
Now they picked up guns.
We'll nip their heads.
Got me?
Veera, l'll not go without SP's wife.
Who said you'll go from here?
Brother, his days are numbered,
give him two more bottles.
Take him to the hill top.
He'll kill himself.
Veera, you're committing a mistake.
He's not our enemy and
what he says is right.
Do one thing, join them,
wear uniform,
they'll give you a gun,
don't search anywhere,
come straight here and kill me.
He's here for a compromise, right?
Why are you refusing it?
Tem trucks of gun and bullets.
Are they here for a compromise?
He's here to check on us.
He's here to know our strength.
- What's our strength?
May l tell? You're our strength.
Our strength is weakening.
l've been watching you,
you're going overboard.
Cool down brother,
l'm asking you also, tell me.
Did anything go fine
ever since she came here?
We are going down.
l think this lady will
take us all down.
You said 14 hours only
but 14 days have passed.
Watch my words, he'll not leave
her even after 14 years.
Will you stop it or not?
Harping on the same thing
Leave me...
- l'm telling you to beat me.
You've courage to beat me
but can't dare ask him.
You don't do anything,
send me with forest officer.
Brother, tell him not to go there.
lt's madness to go there.
lt's wrong to send him alone.
l'll also go with him.
l'll go with him.
No, you may use bad words
that may not go down well,
brother, l'm not a kid,
l've done intermediate,
l know all the laws they speak about.
Just for once, trust and send me.
l'll not spoil your name.
Hey l saw... l saw... where is sir?
l found... went to unreachable
place and met the person.
Give me a medal sir, gold, silver
or bronze, anything will do.
What did you bring with you?
- His brother for a compromise.
But your wife must give the medal.
- Where is his brother?
He's outside.
Where is his brother?
- He's outside.
l've discussed all the issues.
lf you say yes...
Where's the bottle?
Who is it? Chakri?
Come out bravely.
No need to fear.
l'm alone.
Look!
l've emptied my gun.
Two conditions.
Must withdraw all the cases,
special team must go back.
You're speaking like a police man.
Your wife is still with us.
She's still alive.
You're still warning us.
You must be in police force.
l'm here for a compromise.
l too wish that only.
No more fights, no more deaths.
Send Ragini to me,
l'll guaranty your brother's life.
lf you want to talk to me, come out.
l'll be in my tent.
Shall l tell my brother that
you're ready for the compromise?
This time it's just a scratch.
Next time l'll not miss it.
Don't run.
This is a no-holds-barred war...
Challenging with blasts all around...
Furious raging battle...
When enemy attacks,
take on him with all might...
Win the battle...
lf you step on the bridge,
l can't guaranty for your life.
He's coming... the officer is
coming on two legs...
He has come.
lf you win...
Where is Ragini?
Where is Vennela?
Where is my sister?
You can't survive today,
pray to your God.
Come... . come... .
No gun, no uniform, no troops.
Got caught alone.
Come... come...
Leave my hand.
Leave my hand, die!
Where is he?
What happened?
He's Lord Rama and
l'm 10 headed Ravana, right?
He's alright, isn't he?
l can't beg more than this.
Answer me.
Tell me.
Hold this.
ls he alive?
Last time l saw him,
he was hale and healthy,
Hanging to the bridge on one hand.
Angrily... furiously... like a hero.
Hold it tightly.
You may leave it.
Wait, l'll check and tell.
Where are you man?
Are you there, SP?
You won't believe but he's
crawling up like a snake.
Will you please do me a favour?
Only God grants boons, l'm a demon.
Don't kill my husband.
lf you come up, only one will survive.
l can leave this rope.
- Only one will live.
l can shoot you.
- lf you...
Do you think l'll give you a loaded gun?
l was waiting all these years
who would kill me.
Fire at me.
lf you fire, just ten minutes.
The bad intentions and
thoughts in my heart...
lt'll die along with me.
But if you shoot here, just a moment,
memories, desires, love, breath,
all will go at a time.
No pain.
Looking at you happily...
with a smile on my face...
l'll die.
lf l stay here...
will you spare his life?
Will you stay?
Really?
What's this?
14 days?
You said you'll take me
in 14 minutes.
l was scared.
l've come back, Dev.
Where is he?
Who? Why?
l'm back, right?
What else you want?
Look at me.
- Where is he hiding?
Did you come for me or for him?
He escaped hiding behind a woman.
Forget about him, Dev.
l'll come back for you.
Let's go home.
Did he beat you?
Did he scare you?
No.
Did he touch you?
lf anything had happened...
He kept you in captive for 14 days.
14 days and 14 nights.
l can understand what you're asking.
Look at me.
Can't you see it yourself?
Are you ready for a lie detector test?
Machine will find the lie.
Aren't you ashamed to ask like that?
When you're saying truth,
why are you scared of a machine?
l somehow managed to hold
my life for 14 days,
but your mean words are killing me.
Truth sometimes is very mean.
What is truth?
How would you know it is truth?
He told me.
Who? What?
My hand is holding your hand,
but your wife is not chaste.
He said not pure.
No... l don't believe it.
He wouldn't told that.
He told me a lot more things.
Shall l say it in details?
- Stop it.
Pull the chain, l'll get down.
Don't threaten me.
You're literally throwing me out.
You're lying and l don't like it.
l'm not lying.
- You're lying.
Lie is written all over your face.
Epitome of lies.
l can see it in your eyes.
You shouldn't have come back.
l shouldn't take you
to Veera's hideout.
But you want to meet him.
l don't know why you're here.
lf you've revenge in heart,
please go away.
The respect he has for you
will remain intact.
Don't know when he'll come and
how long you've to wait.
l've kept food and water.
You've come back.
What did you tell him about me?
l'm breathless,
l can't hear anything.
My ears are numbed.
Am l the weapon to win over him?
l'm feeling dizzy with happiness.
Don't get angry on me.
What did you tell Dev?
What did you tell him?
Tell me.
Veera, leave my hand.
Leave my hand... let me die.
He said let me die.
Hold tightly,
l can kill you for your wife.
For the same wife's sake
l can spare your life.
Leave you or save you?
Shall l leave you?
Did you say anything bad about me?
A good wife for a bad man.
Through the test of fire...
... pure gold.
We are cheap men but never allowed
even wind to touch the pure gold.
Nothing else?
Go... take her away before
l change my mind.
Hold on to me... come up.
That's it.
Veera is happy, why are you sad?
Held you in captive for
Are 14 days so long?
Didn't feel so much when
l left you blindfolded?
But why am l so happy
on your coming back?
Please don't cry.
Stop!
l don't like women crying.
My life has come alive.
lt has started breathing.
Dev told me wrong.
He never listened to me.
Why did SP speak bad about you?
Without any reason?
Suspected me.
- Suspected you?
SP?
Great... excellent!
- Dev is not here.
You're very smart.
He doesn't know l've come for you.
You know very well who
can lead you to me.
Come out.
Come...
l told you l'll come back for you.
SP! Shoot me.
Shoot me... . shoot me...
Shoot me!
Not just one shot, fire ten times.
Spray hundreds of bullets.
Shoot me... . shoot me...
Shoot me... .
Ragini, move aside.
You can't kill my happiness.
Move!
You can't kill.
Fly away... fly away...
End of a story...
Heart is at peace with death... .
The spring will not come back again...
Will my pain ever ease?
ln this eternal world...