-How dare you hit us?
-Don't hit me
-With whom are you playing?
-Go!
-Who are you all?
-Go
Who are you?
Why do you pour it?
Don't fire!
Seems he is coming to dash us
lt will break
Turn your boat.
Don't come close
RAAVANAN
VlKRAM
AlSWARYA RAl BACHCHAN
PRlTHVlRAJ
KARTHlK
Name is Veera
But has hundred nicknames
PRABHU
Very courageous
PRlYAMANl
You decide the fate
You can Be good or Bad
You're a mix of
Both good and Bad
Why were you Born?
What path did you take?
Why did you take up the war?.
You're a mix of
Both good and Bad
Photography
Santhosh Sivan, V.Manikandan
Music
A R RAHMAN
Direction
MANl RATNAM
Sir! Hemanth is on the line!
Yes, Hemanth!
Sir, l don't know how to put it
What?
Tell me Hemanth
There's been an accident
A boat accident, sir
ln that..
When? Where?
ln the past hour
Near Padayaar Padithurai
Your wife's been kidnapped
-Who's responsible?
-Veera's men
They're headed toward the hills
A search has been initiated
A special task force is coming
Anyone there?
The men here. Don't think twice
before wringing necks
Who?
Who are you?
Delicious chicken curry
Want a bite?
Why did you bring me here?
Who's that?
Who is that?
l'm not scared of you
No guts to fight a man...
...so you pick on a woman
O heart, fear not! ln this life
Victory will be yours
Freedom and peace..
..is yours through devotion
The Goddess's blessings are with you
We're no enemies
O heart, fear not
in this life...
Victory will be yours...
Of your many sins,
the worst sin is abducting me
-She will die
-She won't
14 hours to go before we
blow her funeral conch
Let her swim some more
Can't you see?
lt's the police
Too busy to answer, eh?
Speak out
Open the gate
-l swear..!
-You moron
Can't you see who is coming here?
l missed a beat again
-In the BuIIock cart..
-You drunkard
You BuIIock cart
wiII you accompany with me?
You go now and come tomorrow
-What's that? -Shut it!
Open the gate -Ok!
Catch!
-Smart men never win
-Return the gun. -Go man!
You drunkard
-Especially one without a gun
-Catch him! -Do you wan to catch?
-I swear I am a watch man!
-Come down
Come down. Or you're dead
As if you could fly like me.
l am going to escape
Here..!
He is climbing
-So you're Gnyana Prakasam?
-Yes sir
-Are you a forest guard?
-For 28 years
-The Forestry Department praises you
-ls it sir?
-You have a record for
getting suspended. -Yes, sir!
Suspended now, sir.
But, two months whizz by..
Know your way round the forest?
Or only round a bottle?
ls your leaping about
thanks to alcohol?
You playing decoy?
Sir, you're a
government servant, inspector
with a great track record
A top police officer
l'm a government servant too.
A-one forest guard
l've been waiting
for 3 hours for you
l won't let you go alone, sir
l don't trust him.
He's a drunk
Could be Veera's man
Can't tell his arse from his elbow
l don't trust him.
He has a short fuse
A right idiot
He's clueless about the forest
and everything else
l'll box your ears
Will you box my ears?
Are you from Thoothukudi?
l like Thoothukudi folk.
But you could be the exception
l should let you lose
among the forest beasts
-Escape..!
-l'll kill you idiot
Veera. Also called Veerayya
Born in Vikrama Singhapuram
Every local police station
has a file on him
63 charges against him
l was transferred here
to finish him off
Ambasamudram Circle
No reception!
No escort
l know you don't care for all that
l believe that many people here
do not like the police
ls that true?
l'll stay far away from such people
Excepting one...
...the man they call Raavanan
The ten-headed Raavanan
Shake the central head,
the others will shake too
Shall we give it a go?
His elder brother Singarasu
is Veera's front man
The lawmaker
Brother Sakkarai is somewhat educated
He settles disputes
Veera consoles when blood is shed..
..and takes revenge for any killings
Why can't you arrest him?
We needed an lnspector like Dev
The other lnspectors feared Veera
What are do?
Guardian angel to some
Terror to others.
And to us..
Veera is a lawbreaker and violent man
A terrorist
The police are supposed to
protect us from men like him
You must stop him.
Shoot him
l had a chance to get this Raavanan
but he got away
This time l will get him
l won't rest till l do
Be brave till then, Ragini
lnspector. Stop here
Just a moment
ln the forest ears are
as useful as eyes
Thoothukudi! Look, he's here
Who tied you up?
Stop chewing.
Are you the boatman?
You gasping?
Get some water for him
What? He said you'd come
and untie me?
He said we'd come
and untie you?
Come on, tell me
They asked you to come
to the mountaintop..
..if you are very smart
Veera ties him up and tells
him where he's headed
Are we looking for him?
Or is he looking for us?
Right?
-Mountaintop -He asked us to come
to the mountaintop
Tell to sir
Did you see her?
ls she all right?
ls she hurt?
Was she crying?
Leave me
l won't come
What are you doing?
You will be ruined
Our curse won't leave you
May you suffer all your life.
You'll pay for your husband's sins
Who are you to kill me?
Who gave you that right?
Why must l pay for men
who fight each other?
My life is mine.
lt belongs to me
Stop!
Not another sound
Already 10 voices in my head
Veera! Kill her. Don't hesitate
Shoot her
-l won't die.
-Damn you!
End the wretch's life.
Let the world know
You can't kill me
The voices in my head
Shiva dancing in fury
A question
An answer
Eternal dilemmas
Anger, Calm, Revenge, Peace
-You can't kill me
-Die laughing
-You'll laugh for 7 lives.
-l won't die
-lf not, you won't..
-My end isn't in your hands
You foolish girl!
When you were Born on this earth?
Why you Iit a spark in my mind?
The teak forest is taII and mighty
A matchstick has no height
Yet the faIIing matchstick
Sets the teak forest on fire
I die Bit By Bit
seeing the quiver of your Iip
O BeIoved, I impIore you
Give me your heart
Standing on the other shore,
Ionging to reach you
Enough! You're hurting my ears
l said stop
l'm not crying
Swallow your tears now
Come
Find yourself another
woman to follow you
Have you no shame?
You coward, abducting a woman
All the abuse in the world
was made for you
Bravo, Veera! The weeping has stopped
Better to hear swear words
than a woman's sobs
The circIing sun and moon
come together in a Iine
ABstinence and honesty Iose their grip
I die Bit By Bit
Seeing the quiver of your Iip
O BeIoved, I impIore you
Give me your heart
Standing on the other shore,
Ionging to reach you
A fruit that scorches
is desired fruit aII the same
This story is a story toId Before
A few aIways defy the ruIes
Man creates ruIes
exceptions too
Even goats look before jumping
Can't you use your brains?
Why did you save me?
Vultures wouldn't prey on you
Then why did you?
Killing you was in my fate
Some bastard erased it
Pray, if you believe in God
Your end is in my hands
lt is written in stone
What did you say?
No bastard will erase
your death from my fate
Gazing at the faraway sun,
the Iotus comes to flower
Light rays may separate them,
But their Bond is strong
Is it a Bud? Or poisonous weed?
Can't teII them apart
The poison spreads
But the heart is ever fearIess
One day I wiII meet my end
WiII your face fade from my eyes?
I Iay Buried with you in my heart
The circIing sun and moon
come together in a Iine
ABstinence and honesty Iose their grip
I die Bit By Bit
Seeing the quiver of your Iip
O BeIoved, I impIore you
Give me your heart
Standing on the other shore,
Ionging to reach you
A fruit that scorches
is desired fruit aII the same
Veera, they're waiting for you
Move along
Veera is coming
-How are you?
-Go away!
l now understand
why you didn't kill her
What a fool!
lt escaped me
One bullet would have done the trick
A case would be filed. Sakkarai
and l would serve five years for you
The problem will be solved
But you have a plan
What plan?
ln only 14 hours the lnspector...
...panics and brings truckloads of men
What would've happened in 14 days!
What a plan!
A gun my hand...
Two minutes from her death
But in her eyes
not a grain of fear
How to kill someone
who isn't scared of dying?
lf you were in my place,
what would you have done?
l don't have a brilliant
my mind to think so far
Ask for a tasty goat soup.
l'll make it
Ask me to fix someone
or send him to jail
lt's done
But all this business of women,
their courage, way beyond me
This is no circus. Go!
No sari shops here
A plantain leaf. My size
Wrap it round and tuck it
in with a pin. Try it!
Go away!
l will tell you
Didn't l tell you to scoot?
Doesn't fear guns nor has any humour
What a life!
Some food. Treat it better
Throw it away!
l'm not an animal you tie up and feed
Be grateful. For generations
We've sweated blood to get food
-Your snobby attitude
-And your attitude?
Ah! Women
l felt sorry for her,
brought her clothes and food
Even my wife doesn't talk to me like that
Eat, if you're hungry
lf you regard me an enemy, don't eat
lt's up to you
Now you've eaten our salt,
you'll have to be loyal to us
For always
-Go and watch out
-A pistol shot
Maybe it is
They're telling us where they are
Greetings! Don't be scared
The lnspector is here.
Ask them, sir
Where is Veera?
Where is he?
Veera is a soft-spoken sage
What rubbish!
A sage? Get lost, you
He's fearless
He is a match for anyone
-That's it!
-Even the God of Death
These men don't know anything
Sir, his heart is clear as water
He's like a mother to us
Likes a bit of mischief
and creates some problem
Creates some for us too
A poet. He speaks in verse
Great poet Thiruvalluvar?
Women go crazy over him
Not all women
Go!
From pantomime to street theater
he excels in everything
A Great comic, splits your sides
And your liver burns
Go
He's dangerous
Drinking, killing, fighting
and womanizing
He has every vice
and his drum-playing...
He seems like the God of Death
-No escaping death.
-Stop
You're confusing me with your
10 accounts of him
My head spins
Your hand..
...is so rough
When our marriage was arranged...
...and our horoscopes matched...
...my mother didn't ask
if you had soft skin
My precious dancer,
a police officer has dangerous hands
Are these hands unsoiled?
Cross your heart and tell me
-O wise saint, l'll tell you
-Naughty
Dearest heart-thief
O dweIIer in eyes
See me with your hands
HoId me with your eyes
Teach me the art of Iove
Lost in thought of you,
my eyes know no sIeep
Master, my master
How much I adore you
Grace me with your Iove
With every passing week,
my Iove grows
Wrap me around your Being
Need I teII you of my desires?
Can't you discover them?
Your touch Brings me aIive
Come. RuIe my heart
The TamiI Ianguage
expresses every nuance
And you?
Do you know Iove's nuances?
Dearest heart-thief
l came here running
when he told me about you
What are you blabbering?
Come
l'm scared.
Oh my goddess!
Get out of there!
Come out!
Be a man
l didn't do it. l swear
lt wasn't me. l promise
l know nothing
Out with the truth!
No trouble getting here?
What's this?
A watch
The one l gave you?
l gave you my sister too
Where is she?
-l don't know
-Did you lose her?
-Out with it! -You didn't lose the watch,
but you lost my sister
-The watch was safe
-Ask him to let me go
-l don't know anything.
-Where is my sister?
Trust me.
Ask him to let me go
Veerayya, believe me,
l know nothing
Growl like villains!
The photo should scare them
Hey, camera! Start clicking
You clicking?
Or must l click you?
The lnspector's wife
is flapping like a bird
Thump her on the head.
She'll stay still
A scarecrow
lt wouldn't even scare the crows
Careful!
Find out where the nearest hospital is
Bring the truck inside
The first-aid box!
His blood is clotting.
He must be taken to a hospital
Leave us alone
Bring the stratcher.
Where is the ice box?
Veera's brother-in-law?
Right?
-He cut my hand off
-l thought you were family
-The animal cut my hand off.
-ls it?
But why leave you here
with a severed hand?
The pain is killing me
Take me to a hospital, sir
Dressed you in my wife's clothes
What's he trying to tell me?
No sir
-lt's paining..!
-Why did he send you?
-My hand pain is killing me...
-ls he scaring me?
Will he cut off my hand too?
Where are you?
They'll kill me
if you don't come soon
Are you trying to see
how brave l am?
l'm not that brave
l'm just pretending
l scream..
..and put up a brave front
Have you given up, Dev?
Answer me!
When will you come?
Hey lady!
Scream away.
Your God won't come
-Or your husband
-Here!
Some food. Take it
Eat it and sleep.
Calm down
She'll eat. Let's go
-The tape is running.
-lts working -Talk now
Hello lnspector
Greeting!
How are you?
Not well, l hope
Our troubles are caused
by big shots like you
lt's Veerayya
Poor, uneducated
Not high born like you
So, an enemy. The villain
Did you see the photo?
Recognise her?
We took it for you with great care
Keep it safe.
Or you may lose it
lf she doesn't return
you'll at least have the photo
Are you angry?
lt hurts, right?
Does grief weight
heavy on the heart?
We abducted one woman
from your home and...
...the police rampage through the forest
Trampling elephant to mosquito
Are your women fragile flowers?
And ours mere gravel?
lnspector, pray..
..that your wife won't suffer
the same fate as our sister
Keep the photo safe
Anyone there?
Stop
Where to?
Be good. Go back.
Tie yourself up. And sleep
Understand?
O forest girI!
O forest girI! Where do you BeIong?
WiII she Bring rain? Or thunder?.
Or vanish?
On seeing her pure face
the forest heaved a sigh
Lightning struck
The heart quickened
O forest girI! Where do you BeIong?
My Iife is desiring for you
This wretched heart of mine
Ioses aII controI
O heart of mine
Let me go home
O forest girl! Where do you belong?
WiII she Bring rain? Or thunder?.
Or vanish?
O forest girI!
O forest girI! Where do you BeIong?
WiII she Bring rain? Or thunder?.
Or vanish?
-The river is flowing Iike a deer..
-Let's push her into the water
-It is flowing Iike a deer..
-Oh gosh!
Rasathi come up!
Hey Veera uncle has come
-We pushed Rasathi into water.
-Rotate it fast
Rotate it fast
Rotate it a little faster
-She looks like one of us.
-Yes
Hey Kuruvamma!
Send me back or tie me up
Wander in the sun with us
and turn dark like us
She is staring at you
-Why don't you stay with us?
Where are you going?
Answer me
Will you stay with us or not?
Where is your gun?
-Take out it and shoot me
-Keep quiet. She is angry.
Better that, than asking me
such a question
Very well. Shouldn't have asked
The lnspector shouldn't have met you
Shouldn't have married you
Shouldn't have come here
Shouldn't have done what he did
Shouldn't have wanted to shoot you
You shouldn't have jumped
Shouldn't have saved you
Shouldn't have felt alive
when you opened your eyes
What's done is done.
And can't be undone
My feelings can't be changed
My words can't be taken back
Will you stay?
lf you weren't married...
...would you stay?
Are you eating jungle food?
Corn and yam?
No wedding feast here
We have to make do.
Right, Akaash?
But don't drop anything
Everyone will know our whereabouts
Veera appears to know...
...every step we take
A little forest bird..
..seems to be singing in his ear
''The lnspector is coming
from the East''
Anyone seen this forest bird?
What about you, Ranjit?
How long?
What have you told Veera?
l don't get it, sir
Where we are.
And how many
l can't..
Talk to me
Sir, you're assaulting an officer
Don't you feel ashamed
to be called a police officer?
-l can hit back too, sir
-Just try
-Where is Veera?
-l don't know, sir
Take me to Veera
You stay 6 months or a year,
then you're transferred
We have to live here
My brothers and sisters study here
Who guarantees their safety?
-He's right, sir.
-So..!
You wear a police uniform
and are loyal to Veera?
He is right
-l don't know where he is
-Tell us what you know
We will find Veera
-What's wrong?
-Vehicle has stopped
The fuel cap is missing
Move aside
Sugar
ln all three trucks?
How did they do it?
l am not
l don't know
Sir, the villagers need to cross
the camp to graze their cattle
The lnspector's tent?
Hemanth, here is a problem
they've sabotaged our trucks
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The IoveBird is fiIIed with Ionging
O eIders, marry them today
What shall we cut the tongue?
The nose? Eh?
Ok. How about the ears?
-Your turn next. Shave him
-No..!
Catch him!
Shave his head
My brother lost a bet
He said we'd never return alive
from the police camp
Shave his head
l have seen your husband's palace
And a photo
Not of you. Of me
Snarling like a villain.
Real mean
You..
A demon's photo in a king's tent
Sit him on a donkey
Catch him
SIay them..
...if a Iine is drawn
If a fence is made...
...puII it down
You aIways ruIed. We ruIe now
SIay them..
...if a Iine is drawn
If a fence is made...
...puII it down
Heads Iowered for eons.
Heads heId high now
They want to share a meaI?
Lay out a feast
They want a share of our riches?
Off with their heads
Make the ruIes.
We won't oBey
The sky won't heed rumBIing cIouds
No one can cIaim our ancestors' Iand
We Befriend snakes too.
Open hearted is our cIan
Mess with us.
Invite trouBIe
Born to a Brave mother
When the BuII charges guts spiII..
Our forefathers had
nothing to Ieave to us...
OnIy their Bravery
SIay them...
...if a Iine is drawn
If a fence is made...
...puII it down
The aroma of homemade food
wafts in the air
Sip our water, strong as country Iiquor
Deprived Iives can survive
drought and famine
A cactus can Iive without monsoon rains
StruggIing forever does not
make you poor
Lose dignity. And right away
you have nothing
We honour mother and wife.
And just as proud of our Iand
The soiI of our forefathers
is watered with our BIood
SIay them...
...if a Iine is drawn
If a fence is made...
...puII it down
You aIways ruIed.
We ruIe now
SIay them...
...if a Iine is drawn
If a fence is made...
...puII it down
You aIways ruIed.
We ruIe now
Look at me
Can you hear me?
Open your eyes
Ah! The captive freeing the caged
Nice game
What will you do to him?
Sit him on a buffalo and
pack him off to the God of Death?
ls no one human to you?
When will your savagery end?
When will their savagery end?
You only see the uniform.
Not the man
He's human too
Devoted to his family
Why do you torture him?
Shoot him at once. Kill him.
Stamp him. Shoot him
Answer her question
Answer her
You mother's boy
Fool! Respecting ladies?
Tell her what you did to Vennila
Who's Vennila?
The girl who changed your life
Tell her about Vennila
Our stepsister
The daughter of father's second wife
Vennila was smart. And brave
The only one who didn't fear Veera
She fell in love with a boy
A high society type like you
Veera had to persuade the family that
Vennila could marry him
Hers was the first wedding in the family
She was overjoyed
Lightning struck
The heart quickened
My heart is Iooking for her
On seeing her pure face
it got sunk
-Another henna lady is here
-Send her in
O forest girI! Where do you BeIong?
-Let's go!
-WiII she Bring rain? Or thunder?.
Or vanish?
O forest girI! Where do you BeIong?
WiII she Bring rain? Or thunder?.
Or vanish?
You look nice in a sari
See the man l am?
l came here despite everyone around
Dressed in a sari, escorted by eunuchs
You got away with it.
Otherwise my brothers
would have fixed you
l know Judo and Karate.
l learnt it in school
White belt
No one can touch me
You're scared of no one?
-And now?
-Stop! Are you crazy?
-You said that you're scared of no one
-Close the door. Someone will see us
lf your brothers see me, l'm dead
Show them your Judo Are you nuts?
Don't open the door!
Where did your guts vanish?
-Stop, will you? -Let's show the world
how brave you are. -You..
Damn it. We are caught
Why did you abuse?
Shouldn't l abuse?
-Hide.
-Why?
-Brother is coming
-Where?
l told you to go
Where should l go?
Why has he come now?
-Hey girl
-What? -l am dead
-Open the door
-Can't open it now
-Oh gosh!
-Who's inside?
What are you asking?
Just me and my shadow are here
Someone came to you to apply henna,
isn't it? l know
l'm changing my sari
How can you change your clothes
with henna in your hands?
-There is that lady
-Oh god!
Brother-in-law?
What are you doing here?
Not his mistake.
l asked him to come
And he came running?
l told him to prove
he had the guts
So he comes in a sari?
What are you doing in girls' quarters?
-No reason
-l was holding hands
Who with?
Come here
With which hand you hold her?
Don't harm him
Brother said he'd give him a bike
for our wedding
He'd look a clown riding
with one hand
He should've thought of that earlier
Which hand?
Open your eyes
Look at the time
Two more days till the wedding
Keep your hands to yourself till then
Or you'll be garlanding her
with one hand
Now go
You tell him
Or else, he'll be glued here.
Adorn the garland
101st goat
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The IoveBird is fiIIed with Ionging
O eIders, marry them today
The Bride is so IoveIy
in her wedding sari..
...hopeIess dreamer
Marry them when the trumpet BIows
Get ready, O Bride
The IoveBird is fiIIed with Ionging
O eIders, marry them today
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The Bride has the Iook of Goddess Sita
ResemBIing Shoorpanaka,
Iying on her Bed
The Bride is so IoveIy
in her wedding sari..
...hopeIess dreamer
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The Bride is deIicate as
newIy picked Iime
But what a chatterBox
Beat the drums tiII they tear
The Brothers-in-Iaw are impatient
to weIcome the groom
Come!
The Bride is here to pay
respects to sister-in-Iaw
Why the deIay?
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The IoveBird is fiIIed with Ionging
O eIders, marry them today
The Bride is so IoveIy
in her wedding sari..
...hopeIess dreamer
Marry them when the trumpet BIows
Get ready, O Bride
Father said l must pay my respects
No pretend tears
You're like the star Sivaji Ganesan
Seeing you any sister would cry
The groom knows already...
...when we give,
we don't take back
Brother!
All of you come!
The sacrificiaI goat is cooking in
the cIay kiIn, drinks pouring
The IoveBird is fiIIed with Ionging
O eIders, marry them today
Stop! No place here for big shots
Our new groom!
We have the invitation and
we're here to bless the couple
Damn it blessings!
-Come brother!
-Leave me!
Our new groom!
-Move aside.
-No, marriage is going on
PIay the nuptiaI drums
Sing a song and dance
Our new groom!
l beg you, go away
Hey groom!
Brother!
Dev must have had
a good reason
lt can't be his fault
The fault is mine
Brother!
Eight men pulled me away
l shouldn't have left Vennila alone
l should've obeyed my conscience
Veera should have known
l didn't think that
the groom would run away
Vela, don't go
This mother's boy...
...took my Vennila from
wedding to police station
Tell me in which rat hole
is your brother hiding?
Till then you stay
l'll get you talking
So what if you're a woman
Talk to me
The police have sharp noses
Sniff him out
You will get ruined
Your family wouldn't prosper
l'll cut your nose off
You took her to the police station
Didn't you?
Are you badly hurt?
Can't you speak?
Never mind
You can't squabble with me now
l can say anything l want
You can't argue with me
Sister-in-law, did you see my husband?
How quickly he ran
Tail between his legs
Who wants a husband like that?
Why did l want to marry him?
Better to stay unmarried like you
But who the hell are the police...
...to have ruined my wedding?
l wasn't scared
They asked me that
your husband has scurried off
So with whom will you
spend your nuptial night?
l swore at them
l begged, 'Don't do it'
But l couldn't stop them
l told myself l would soon be home
They wouldn't let me go
l screamed and begged
They didn't leave me
The bastards took turns.
All night
My life is in tatters
l lost everything
Vennila!
Watch out
Pull it
Slowly!
Come fast
-Get a blanket
-l will
You're nothing to worry
They've stripped him of everything
No hair. No dignity.
Nothing left
He's breathing
You're still alive.
Damn the rest
-You don't worry
-Where's that blanket? Hurry
-Don't worry.
-l am bringing it, sir
Can you hear me, Hemanth?
l'll tell you one thing
A stiff drink will...
-Hurry up
-Lift him. -Ok sir
He was there for a few hours
And madam? For 8 days
-Enough!
-l say ''enough'' too
-Take him to camp..
-When big convoys like ours advance,
..everyone knows.
Even the ants
They'll take us one by one
and make us bald
Any bright ideas?
One, sir. l need your permission
That's enough
Give me strength
Don't take my anger away
Anger gives me the will to live
Stop them from showing
compassion to me
l beg you
Don't show bad people in good light
Nor show them as truthful
Give me the courage to fight
My anger cannot lessen
Can't you do that much for me?
Did l barge in like a bull?
What kind of man is he?
Your inspector
A good man...
...or a very good man?
God-like, enough?
God-like?
Divine?
An ideal man?
A man with no flaws?
Won't ten heads together equal him?
Not even close
What's he like? Good-looking?
Handsome, no doubt
What else would you expect?
l must see him.
At least once
To see what he's like in person
l should ask him
why he met you first
ls he loving?
Does he make you laugh?
And you...
Do you love him?
l feel jealous
A burning ache deep inside
Does your god feel jealous too?
No. Only Veera does
The downtrodden, the uncouth brute
Not a match to you
Or your God-like husband
But jealousy has made me
suddenly feel matchless
lt has made me suddenly feel invincible
This demon of jealousy..
..has made me all-powerful
Where are you?
lt will be tasty if we add more..
Don't say no
l'm a forest guard..
Do you eat sour fruit?
Bite the onion
and swallow the sour fruit
lmagine it's a feast
A wedding feast is very tasty!
Your husband has sent me to find you
Searched every inch of the forest
Glad you're ok, Mrs. lnspector
He gave me a keepsake.
lt is in my pocket
What was that noise?
Madam, here.
Look behind you
Trust me. l'll carry you
away on my shoulders
And take you to your husband
Why didn't Dev come?
He's five kms away
His convoy makes such a ruckus,
everyone knows when they move
So l came up ahead
Don't hesitate
They are wild people.
They aren't kind
Say the word
-We'll throw chilli
in their eyes and escape -Oh God!
Don't hurt him.
You already have me captive
l am going to slay
him like a goat
Will you throw chilli at us?
Your death-knell too
l hear many sounds
The inspector's convoy is
heading this way
Watch out
l may be from the lnspector's party
But l'll vote for you
Look around you
They will do anything
for you. Even die
Am l wrong?
They will do
You've done so much for them
But l ask you, why would you
want to risk their lives?
You're the only one who'll die
You will die with in a minute..
Send madam back with me.
Stop this quarrel
We'll drop all charges
-What if we don't send her back?
-Go man
He hears the whole story.
Still gets it back to front
Need l answer?
The end of the world
All over and done with
Old man, explain
Brother, he says it'll be the
end of the world. All over
Must we shake with fear?
-Hey! -What brother?
-Are you shaking?
l am shaking
-Are you scared of dying?
-Why should we have fear?
-Anyone scared?
-Why are you asking like that?
No one seems scared.
So now what?
Throw stones at a dog.
lt will bark and then bite you
Force a tree branch down and let go
lt will spring up with greater might
What's new in your threats?
We've heard it all before
They hit us.
We hit back
They caned us.
We did the same
The bastards point guns at us now
We'll snap your necks. Understand?
Veera, l won't leave
this place without madam
Who said you were leaving? Eh?
Brother! His end is near
Get him a drink.
Leave him at the cliff
He'll roll down himself
You're making a bad mistake
He isn't against us.
He's right
Go to the lnspector then
Get yourself a uniform
Come back and
plough me with bullets
He's talking of peace
Why be angry?
With ten trucks of ammunition?
Talking of peace?
He's sniffing around to see
if we're strong
What is our strength?
Shall l tell you? You are
That strength is our weakness now
l am observing,
you are arguing with him
Be quiet, brother
l am asking you too
Everything has gone wrong
since she got here
A curse has fallen on us
The witch will burn us all
You said she'd die in 14 hours.
That became 14 days
Not in 14 years he will let her go
-Will you stop it? Why do you
repeat it again? -Hit me
You can hit me
You dared to hit me
But you don't dare question Veera
You don't do anything.
Let me go with the forest guard
Make him see sense
lt is mistake going
to the police
lt's mistake.
Sending him alone is a mistake
l'll go with him
You can't open your mouth
without swearing
How can you talk peace?
Brother, l am not a child.
And l've studied till Plus two
l know the law
Give me a chance.
Trust me
l won't let you down
l've seen her
Where is sir?
l found her whereabouts
l went where no one goes
And saw the captive one
l deserve a medal.
Gold or silver. Anything
-ls Veera here?
-His brother is here. To talk peace
My medal?
You Mrs..
-Where's his brother?
-Waiting, sir
All negotiating done
lf you say over,
everything will be finished
Where is my BottIe?
Who is it? Sakkarai?
Come out
l'm alone
Just me
Come and see
The gun isn't loaded
Two conditions
Drop aII charges against us
And take your men and go
You talk just like a police officer
Your wife is with us
She's still alive for now
ls that a threat?
Join the police force
l came here to talk peace
l want peace too
No more bad blood
Send Ragini back
Veera will come to no harm
Come out when you want to talk
l'll be waiting in my tent
Do l tell Veera
you're ready to make peace?
lt's only a scratch
Next time you won't be so lucky
-Veera told me, but l didn't
listen his words. -Don't run
Hurry up!
A BattIe cry rings out
Like angry seas, two great armies
rush to the attack
Deafening as thunder,
chariots hurtIe forward
''An end to your arrogance.
The battle has begun''
Like angry seas, two great armies
rush to the attack
Deafening as thunder,
chariots hurtIe forward
''A warless day is no day''
''He will come with an army
and dethrone you''
Hemanth, careful
Keep coming and you'll die
A round of applause!
He isn't running.
He's flying
Where is Ragini?
Where is my sister?
Where is Vennila?
Where is she?
This is the day you'll die
Say your prayers
''The virtuous tumbling to hell''
Come, sweetheart
No gun, no uniform, no back up
Just you and me
Come to me
Veera, let go
Let him plummet to his death
Screaming
Where is he?
What's happened to him?
He's God for you
And me?
The ten-headed demon
Tell me he's all right
Don't make me beg
Say something
Tell me
Hold this
Alive? Right?
Seemed damn fit when
l last saw him
He was dangling...
...with one hand from a bridge
Spitting fire.
So gutsy. A real hero
Hold tight
Don't you let go
Where's that lnspector?
Where is he?
There he is
Amazing. Slithering like a snake
Do me a favour
Only Gods do favours.
Not demons
Don't kill Dev
Come up and face me alone
l'll let go
-Only one beast can survive
-l can shoot you
Who do you bet on?
Think l'd give you a loaded gun?
l have always wondered
who would end up killing me
Shoot me...
...and, in a few minutes...
...the turmoil and the suffering
Everything will be snuffed out
Aim here.
And in an instant...
Memory
Love
Desire.
Your very life
All gone. ln one go
Painless
Looking at you, l'll die contented
With a smile on my face
And if l stayed, will you spare him?
Will you stay?
Are you sure?
What are you doing?
You have a beard?
A 14-day growth?
You should've come for me in 14 minutes
You had me scared
l'm back now
At last, l came to you
Where is he?
Why do you ask?
l'm here
What more do you want?
Where's he hiding?
Did you come for me?
Or Veera?
He left you here and escaped
Let it go
l'll be back
Take me home
Let's go home
Did he hit you?
Did he threaten you?
No
Did he touch you?
What happened that shouldn't have?
They kept you for 14 days
14 days and 14 nights
l know what you're asking
Look at me.
Can't you tell?
Will you take a lie detector test?
We'll soon know
How dare you talk like that?
lf you aren't lying,
why does the test bother you?
l just about survived 14 days
Now l wish that l were dead
The truth is sometimes harsh
How do you know the truth?
He told me
Who told you? What?
My hands may be defiled
But your wife is not pure as gold
She's sullied
lmpossible. l don't believe it
He couldn't have said that
He said a lot more.
Shall l go on?
Stop
l'm getting off this train
Don't threaten me
Are you throwing me out of your life?
l don't like your lies
l never lie, Dev
But you're lying now
Your face... all lies
Your body... more lies
lt shows in your eyes
You shouldn't have come back
Even if l knew where Veera was,
l shouldn't tell you
But you're asking me
to take you to him
l don't know why you came back
lf you are still angry on him,
kindly go home
Let Veera keep the regard he has for you
l don't know how long
you'll have to wait
l've left you something to eat
You're back
What did you tell Dev about me?
l'm out of breath.
l really can't hear you
l can't hear you?
Am l the weapon to defeat him?
l'm dizzy with happiness
Don't be harsh
What did you tell Dev?
What did you say?
Tell me
Hey, Veera
Let him plummet to his death
He'll die screaming
Hold on tight
l could kill you to win your wife
And l could spare you for her
Shall l leave you or save you?
Shall l leave?
What did you say about me?
You have a wife, pure as gold
Throw gold into fire..
..it becomes purer
Our hands may be defiled
But we have...
...protected your wife with great care
What else did you tell him?
Take her and go
before l change my mind
Hold
Come yourself up
Veera is so happy,
how can you be upset?
Were you captive for only 14 days?
Only 14 days?
Why do 14 days
sometimes feel like a lifetime?
l didn't feel so bad when l sent
you back, blindfolded
But why do l feel such happiness today?
No tears
Swallow those tears
l don't like women crying
l feel alive again
l can breathe again
Dev said vile things.
He didn't heed a word l said
Why did he talk like that?
Without any reason?
-He distrusts me
-Distrusts you?
The lnspector?
Well done!
Dev isn't here
Dev, you're so devious
Dev doesn't know l'm here
He really knows how to get to me
Come out
Show yourself
l told you l'd come back
Go on, shoot
Shoot me
Not once. You'll have to
shoot me ten times
A hundred times
Shoot me
Shoot me!
Ragini, move
You can't destroy my happiness
Move
You can't destroy it
I wiII come again
Come Back to foIIow you
Is Iife a mere scriBBIing of a chiId..
..in which meaning is sought?
Life changes and ends
when the meaning is unraveIed
Subtitles by ringo